Hossein Sabouri . Jarvis Consulting

Using Nuke as a main software when I was working for visual effect companies for a couple of years attracted me to the computer science. I honed my computer skills by graduating from Concordia University with a Graduate Diploma in Computer Science degree. Gained my quality assurance analyst expertise by joining to Morgan & Stanley company which gave me the opportunity to hand-on experience working closely with full-stack features teams to deliver complete components for boarder platform integration and leveraged various technologies and tools, including LINUX, SQL, GIT Bitbuckets, Object Oriented Programming (OOP), and delivered work using Agile (Kanban) methodologies, analyzed requirement and performed functional and regression tests based on developer instruction.

Skills

Proficient: Java, Python, Linux/Bash, RDBMS/SQL, Agile/Scrum, Git

Competent: Donec, fermentum, Donec, fermentum, Donec

Familiar: Docker, Selenium, jira, REST APIs, C++

Jarvis Projects

Project source code: https://github.com/jarviscanada/jarvis_data_eng_demo

Cluster Monitor [GitHub]: Deployed a project to collect hardware specification and also monitor the cluster nodes resource usage in real time. The collected data will be stored in an RDBMS database for this we use posgres sql database. The data can help to manage reports for future resource planning purposes.

Core Java Apps [GitHub]:

- Twitter App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- JDBC App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.
- Grep App: Curabitur laoreet tristique leo, eget suscipit nisi. Sed in sodales ex. Maecenas vitae tincidunt dui, et eleifend quam.

Springboot App [GitHub]: Not Started

Python Data Analytics [GitHub]: Not Started

Hadoop [GitHub]: Not StartedSpark [GitHub]: Not Started

Cloud/DevOps [GitHub]: Not Started

Highlighted Projects

Web app for resturant [GitHub]: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Machine Learning: Suspendisse a tincidunt odio. Suspendisse posuere luctus aliquet. Quisque magna tellus, tempor vitae arcu sed, volutpat scelerisque lacus. Aliquam varius pulvinar dapibus. Ut a tincidunt sem. Aenean sollicitudin fringilla erat ut imperdiet. Phasellus fermentum, enim vitae laoreet elementum, eros nisl hendrerit lorem.

Professional Experiences

QA Analyst, Jarvis (2023-present): Developed multiple software application and worked on projects using Linux Bash, Docker and more. Agile/Scrum was used to collaborate with team.

QA Analyst, Morgan & Stanley (2022-2023): Analysed requirements and performed functional and regression tests based on developers instruction. Executed TCM to deploy new changes and created test cases for different scenarios. Delivered work using Agile (Kanban) methodologies, ensuring that all work was on track and met necessary deadlines.

Image Compositor, Double Negative (2017-2021): Combined visual elements from separated sources into single image by Nuke in Linux environment. Worked with software Nuke and Fusion, Conversion 2D image to 3D. Harvested Nuke script in order to extract the layer image elements

Education

Concordia University (2018-2021), Graduate diploma, Computer Science, Department of Computer Science and Software Engineering - N/A - N/A - GPA: 3.03/4.5

Concordia University (2011-2014), Bachelor of Fine Art, Mel Hoppenheim School of Cinema - N/A - N/A - SPA: 3.14/4.5

Iran University of Science and Technology (1993-1998), Bachelor of Science, School of Metallurgy and Materials Engineering - N/A - N/A - GPA:

Miscellaneous

- Udacity Machine Learning (2019)
- Winner
- Tennis player
- Soccer player
- Cinephile